[Episode 11]
Why are you...
Halt!
Identify yourselves.
Unhand her.
I said unhand her.
My Lord.
Are you deaf?
Unhand her now!
Get them!
Back away or I'll cut her.
- My Lord.
- Stop this or we'll stop you.
Now!
- Are you alright?
- My Lord.
What are you doing here
at this time of night?
Your orders, Sir?
They look like common criminals.
Hand them over to the local police.
Sir.
The King's not in the palace?
No. He was looking for you
at the Police Bureau.
What?
Well? What were you doing here?
Thank you, My Lord.
You saved my life.
What have I told you?
Go out early.
If I hadn't come by,
who knows what might have happened.
I'm sorry, My Lord,
but this was especially important.
Especially?
I was looking for you, actually.
For me?
For me? Why?
I had to tell you something.
I went to the administrative offices.
You what?
But the guard said
you'd never heard of me.
Why'd you say that, though?
I'm not sure...
Wait! The guard went to Officer Kang,
of course. That's it.
Huh?
There are two inspectors in our office.
Kang's the other one.
- Ah, so that's it?
- Of course. I'd never say that.
Ah, I see. I thought maybe
you'd forgotten me.
So what was so important that
you had to come find me?
Well, it's this way...
What?
The King saved her?
Yes, Sir. The royal guard turned
them over to the local police.
Luckily they're being tried as
common criminals. We're safe on that score.
But what went wrong? The King saving
a servant? Why would he do that?
Sire.
I spoke with the girl on the way here.
Do we really have information
that clears Lady Jang?
Yes, Sire.
Where's the body?
I need to see it.
Sire.
- Show His Highness.
- Sir.
- Now with some pinellia on your hands.
But... How could...
Contact with pinellia would have
discolored the doctor's hands.
That's what happened, Sire.
This proves the pharmacist
didn't send pinellia to Lady Jang.
And Dongyi discovered this?
Yes, Sire.